{
    "id": "a5b41ec0b9264f28be1a884deb34c6c8",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ..................... him yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not meet",
                "did not met",
                "have not met"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5084701f176f44a9ae50d2a43245aec7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t say …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anything",
                "nothing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f23d350c9ef4489588c505279d92c5b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Professionals ……………….. teachers and lawyers should have good communication skills.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such like",
                "such as",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1bbd3a65d7f74303b6d9bd6af5d4e00d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bird is …………….. the nest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "109aeee41d114b0c87aad987d27788b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor ……………… saw me in the afternoon was a middle aged person.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "99a8657a6517436ea7ccf5c65d64119d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked him why ………………… late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he was",
                "was he"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb939613b51f4cf5bbf6a375a9a3de72"
        },
        {
            "question": "Something ………………. to be done about it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "ought",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af3febdb197c4005b19adba553218ee9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She wasn’t ……………….. impressed with the results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quiet",
                "quite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c78707ab609b4023b1e9f2624c966af8"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the ………………. film I have ever seen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "worst"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "97f097e0ca4c4db8bfbdaee6d6a316c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nobody",
                "anybody"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1630dd33bdf44ee789032e7854972852"
        }
    ]
}